In Egypt, an old hag named Enyaba
once told me:
Fire at whomever
the arrow desires.
For the impaled
shall become your ally.
The speared shall witness,
rising from the deep recesses
of their soul, a single unique power.
Stands is what
I think she called them.
Jotaro Kujo and his minions…
If there are more hit men
in Morioh in pursuit of my dear Yoshikage,
then my Stand users,
my allies, shall multiply by my hand.
So, arrow! Whom do you desire?
Select your prey! Go forth!
PULL
A telephone pole?
What does
a telephone pole have t—?
You… You desire that child?
You're trying to tell me
that child will become my ally?
Then so be it.
All I have to do is pierce
the lad's soul, right?
JOJO'S BIZARRE ADVENTURE
DIAMOND IS UNBREAKABLE
A demon's crept into
our everyday life
It's about to take away
something precious
Our peace has already
crumbled long ago
So casually, so nonchalantly
It's taken from us
before we know it
If we want it back,
now's the chance
With the sharpness of
the piercing arrow
The beauty of two souls united
Wherever you go, chase you
Whenever, chase you
I will chase you
Nowhere to escape
Start running, I will chase you
Tomorrow, chase you
My fists will be the one
to show you
Tenacity decides
who will win or lose
So I chase you
EPISODE 26
ROSHAM BOY IS HERE!
So it's Rohan Kishibe,
manga artist extraordinaire.
Good morning, Mr. Joestar.
Snapping a few photos I see…
I'm trying to capture candid shots
of office workers
in their morning commute.
If Yoshikage Kira really did steal
someone's identity at
Beauty Institute Cinderella,
we can safely assume
he's commuting every morning,
just like his victim once did.
Commuting…
Knowing he's a man between
the ages of 25 and 35
around 175 centimeters
tall and an office worker
helps narrow the suspect pool.
I see…
But how do you know
he uses this station…
He could just
as easily commute by car.
That is a possibility.
He may have changed his face,
but, in many ways,
he's likely still very much himself.
You can be sure the family of
one of these men is already
wary of bizarre behavior.
My fear is that the family
will recognize their intruder,
which would likely prompt
him to eliminate them as well.
I'm not getting soft, mind you…
We must simply locate Kira
before he can wreak more havoc.
Hey!
Mister, wanna play roshambo?
Ro-sham…
Come on. Can't ya play a little?
Crazy kid…
Ro-sham…
I suppose every station
has its nut job…
Well, if you happen to
come across any leads,
you know how to reach me, Mr. Joestar.
Don't go sticking your nose
in dangerous situations
all by your lonesome now…
Hey, Mister.
You're that manga drawer, right?
You stopped drawing
for a while, right?
I read Shonen Jump every week.
So whaddya say… It wouldn't kill
ya to play with me.
What's your problem? Beat it!
I just wanna play roshambo.
Come on…
What's with this little punk?
He's got a gaping hole in his cheek!
- It's serious…
- Hey,
- It must open up into his mouth…
- come on, come on!
No hard feelings if you beat me.
If it's a draw, we do it again.
If you're too late, you lose.
Got it? Ready, and…
Ro-sham…
This kid is being
weirdly tenacious.
Is he a Stand user?
Okay… ro-sham…
Heaven's Door!
Hmph.
Let's see…
Name's Ken Oyanagi, age eleven.
Nothing here about a Stand…
The injury seems to be
from a fall from a telephone pole.
"ROSHAMBO" FAN.
WILL PLAY "ROSHAMBO" AT ANY CHANCE.
PLAYS "SCISSORS" FIRST.
So this kid plays roshambo
any chance he can get.
Ridiculous, but…
Hello sirs.
Will you be riding today or not?
Could you please
give me 30 seconds?
Fire away.
Fine, let's go.
Then you'll leave me alone, right?
Ro-sham… bo!
Well, so long.
I-I lost…
I suppose that's enough work
for one day.
Yo, Rohan-sensei.
Calling it a day already, eh?
Why don't you come and join us?
It's that jerk off Josuke,
and that moron Okuyasu…
Not to mention bitchy Yukako.
I have absolutely nothing
in common with any of them.
Sorry, but I'm actually working.
Some other time.
I see…
Hey, just what do you
think you're doing? That's my seat.
You never sat down.
The seat was up for grabs,
so I took it.
Whoops.
What's this all about?
Why won't you leave me alone?
Let's settle this with
a little roshambo.
Winner takes the seat.
Again?!
No! I sat here first!
- This is my seat!
- Sir…
Hang on…
Rohan-sensei, give him a break.
He's just a kid.
Don't make the poor kid cry.
That's not very grown up of you.
You could try sitting next to him…
Shut up! Not another word,
all of you!
Fine! I'll play you
roshambo again!
That's what you want,
isn't it?
Now that's more like it!
Get ready!
Ro-sham… bo!
Oh? Y-Yes, I win!
Whatcha think of me now!
I've never been so happy to
win roshambo in my life.
- Not very grown up like…
There's no better feeling…
than destroying a little whelp
at his own game.
D-Damn it!
This is some good material…
Who knew such an obscure book
could be found in Morioh?
7,500 yen, huh…
Do I have that much on me?
Excuse me,
I wanna buy this book.
You cursed…
Shall we duke it out
roshambo style?
Fine!
Brace yourself! Ro-sham…
Rock!
You're messing
with the wrong artist!
I won. See?
I finally won!
One win, two losses!
What the hell is this?!
Wh—
What?!
It can't be! His wound…
Could he be a Stand user?!
What?!
S-So cool!
Who knew he was hiding
something so cool!
This energy flowing into me
is totally awesome!
I'm feeling energized!
H-Heaven's Door!
Turn this brat into a book!
OPEN
CANNOT ATTACK ROHAN KISHIBE.
This kid…
seems that was the first time
he used his Stand.
Could he be on his way to
becoming a Stand user?
Hmph. "I want to beat the crap
out of Rohan in roshambo," huh?
"Roshambo is not
a game of chance.
It's a psychological
game of will.
If I defeat Rohan at roshambo,
then it means
I've outwitted the man himself.
Rohan Kishibe is only 20 years old,
but he lives life on his own,
and on his own terms.
What's more, he inspires
countless people with his many works.
If I can beat the crap out
of the revered Rohan in roshambo,
I can one day be
even better than him.
One day, I want to grow up
and be revered and
respected like Rohan."
There's no doubt about it,
this kid is well on the road to
becoming a Stand user!
The arrow must have only
just pierced his soul.
"Ability… victory in roshambo means
my opponent's energy becomes my own.
However, five games are necessary.
Two wins means only
partial energy from my opponent."
Five games?
I CANNOT ATTACK ROHAN KISHIBE.
I CAN ATTACK ROHAN KISHIBE.
W-What?
So awesome…
So this power's called a "Stand"?
Thought you dodged
the bullet, eh…
See, I already got
one-third of your Stand.
My right arm is… gone!
I've got one-third of Heaven's Door
under my control!
No more mind-reading for you.
Punk…
If I win two more times,
all of your powers will be mine!
You punk! Think you can
get away with this?!
Pretty ballsy move,
punching me like that.
It's called getting a taste
of your own medicine, ass!
To get Heaven's Door's
right arm back,
I'm going to have to win
at roshambo, eh…
It's game on.
Good!
5 MATCHES
MATCH 1
MATCH 2
MATCH 3
MATCH 4
MATCH 5
HEAVEN'S DOOR
Are you oblivious
to your own plight?
One more loss and
you're finished.
You have to know
you're out of second chances.
Now that I know you're a Stand user,
I shall have no mercy on you!
The moment
I retrieve my right arm,
I'm putting you
out of commission.
And you know it.
Are you trying to
psyche me out?
All right, let's get
this little contest started.
No, I'm not ready quite yet.
I did just win with paper,
and it's only natural to want to
go with rock or scissors next,
then again that'd be
a real childish move.
But you don't seem to
be the naive type, Rohan-sensei,
so maybe going with paper
would be the best way to go.
Right, I made up my mind.
Here we go!
Ro-sham… bo!
What?!
I did it!
I just outwitted Rohan with paper!
ROHAN
KEN
5 MATCHES
That makes two wins
and two losses.
Now, then…
I took your lower half.
If you're tired, maybe we
should take a trip to the bench?
No, that won't be necessary.
The moment of victory
is best savored…
while looking down on the conquered
with pity and disdain.
I've got two wins
and two losses now,
we're both one game away
from destiny.
But now,
I can almost taste victory.
I mean, after I lost twice,
I did win twice in a row.
It's the other way around for you,
Rohan-sensei.
You've lost twice in a row.
You're smack dab in
the middle of a losing streak!
Marvelous!
I'd expect nothing less
from a kid chosen by the arrow!
If this kid can take on
Rohan Kishibe's unique
mind-reading powers,
we'll be invincible!
You will serve my Yoshikage well.
Hey punk…
Your psychological ploys
have improved greatly.
You've lost twice in a row,
that's a fact.
Fact, huh… Indeed.
In that case, allow me to
tell you another fact.
For our next duel, paper will
most certainly not be your choice of attack.
Guess we'll find out,
won't we…
Hey, hey, hey, hey,
hey, hey, hold it.
I used rock twice in
a row and lost.
Which means rock is
my unlucky move.
Am I wrong?
It's only natural I'd be averse
to using my unlucky rock a third time.
Since you said
I was on a losing streak,
you won't be able to use paper.
Your using paper would
be an admission
that I am not in the middle
of a losing streak.
You're going down!
Let's go, Rohan Kishibe!
It's time!
Ro…
…sham…
…bo!
After all that bluffing,
he still used paper.
His mental fortitude is remarkable.
I can't lose!
I'm definitely the one
with winning momentum here!
I'll use paper four times in a row!
This game's in the bag!
All right! Rock!
I'll make misfortune work
in my favor!
One more…
My knees are…
What? He's never moved
like that before!
The only one Rohan hasn't
used yet is scissors…
Crap… Going with paper
four times in a row is risky!
Crap!
I guess rock wasn't unlucky,
after all!
That bastard Rohan!
Th-That's…
Hey, Mister!
Hey, Rohan-sensei. Those two are
probably Stand users, too, right?
They are, right? I can feel it.
Let's see how lucky I really am.
If my luck has run out,
those two will come over here.
If luck is on my side,
they'll never dream of
coming over here.
Hey, look, it's Rohan.
- Hey! Hey!
- I really can't stand that guy.
Let's put on a smile and
mind our own business.
Hmm… Well, hmm…
MENACING
That child…
I would guess he's likely…
just another fan.
See you later.
See ya.
It looks like luck is totally
on my side, Rohan-sensei.
I've never felt more
confident about winning in my life.
I've got luck protecting me!
I feel like I could
survive Russian roulette
With five out of six bullets
in the chamber!
CRASH
Even a shower of glass!
Now, for the final match.
Who's gonna win, Rohan-sensei!
What are you doing?
Hurry up and assume
your roshambo pose.
You're the one who needs to
hurry up and get started.
You're looking at my next move.
You can knock off the jokes, okay.
I can assure you
this isn't a joke.
You said you were going
to surpass me,
but since I've got
nine years on you,
I'll let you in on a little secret…
Beating one's opponents
isn't that difficult.
The real challenge is…
Now pay attention…
outdoing oneself!
I'm going to outdo my own luck!
Let's go, Rohan!
It's on!
Ro-sham… bo!
Yes! How's that, Rohan Kishibe?!
W-What?
- What?!
- Huh?
W-What the—?
Why am I making the rock move?!
That makes three wins
and two losses.
Now you've got the unlucky rock.
It wasn't just Joseph Joestar
who paid me a visit. Luck did too.
The Invisible Baby.
Huh?!
I WILL RESCUE ROHAN FROM DANGER.
I WILL TURN MYSELF INVISIBLE AND
MAKE THE KID'S HAND INTO "ROCK".
You were over-reliant on luck,
whereas I took it upon myself
to change my luck.
That is the meaning of
outdoing oneself.
BOOM
Now, then, as I promised,
I shall now render you
out of commission.
For I'll write,
"I shall never again win
another game of roshambo.
My Stand shall
be reduced to tatters."
Sh-Shut up!
Stay away from me, Rohan!
O-Otherwise, this baby's gonna…
Do you understand
what you're doing?
Hmph! We've moved on now
to a war of words!
You didn't really beat me!
You did nothing
but cheat, you coward!
Surrender the baby, now.
Battle me one more time!
Do that and the baby
remains safe and sound.
What about "surrender the baby"
do you not understand…
I'll humor you.
Get ready to lose!
Ro-sham! Bo! Bo!
I-I-I can't win!
Blast it! I went through all the trouble
to turn you into a Stand user
and you blew it!
Sayonara!
You won't die.
I'm simply going to
wipe out your Stand.
If…
If I have to live life
under the shadow of your writing…
If I have to live under
your psychological control…
I'd rather die under
this giant truck!
Take that, Rohan Kishibe!
PFFT
Bravo. I like you, kid.
It's people who have a flare
for comic book-like action that really…
DASH
pull at my heartstrings!
Wha—?!
Y-You'll be run over, too!
You think so?
What the—? Th-The wind!
Whoa, what the hell
is this picture?!
I-I can't see!
I-It swerved at just
the last second.
Y-You could have died, too,
but, for me, you…
Was it luck?
In a relatively short period,
you've become quite
the extraordinary individual.
I won't render you
out of commission.
However, you must not
use your Stand for evil.
Of course, I had to run into
that damn thing, damn it!
I lost. I've completely lost.
Hey, Rohan!
D-Did you find the baby?
She's missing, Sensei!
N-No, she may've gone
invisible again.
D-Dammit…
She's gone.
Hey, where are you?
I'll just pretend like
nothing ever happened…
W-Where did you go?
Where are you?
Rosham Boy
- Real name: Ken Oyanagi.
- Hey!
Stand name: Boys Man Man.
Not out of commission.
Though, the hole
in his cheek remains.
EPISODE 27
I'M AN ALIEN